Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 28-131)
  - Non-Show Music (Box 92-106, 127-131)
    - College songs
      - Ray Hartley (pianist), Includes scores for album “For Lovers” (RCA Victor LPM/LSP 1870), arranged and conducted by Don Walker ( 1959 )
        - Stand up and cheer interpolation, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 105/5)
        - Stompin' at the Savoy, Full score (Box-folder 105/6)
        - Stouthearted men, Short score, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 105/7)
        - Student prince-selection, Short score/full score (Box-folder 105/8)
        - Sweepin' the clouds away, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 105/9)
        - St. James infirmary, Sketch (Box-folder 105/9)
        - S'wonderful, Full score (Box-folder 105/10)
        - Tango intro, Sketch (Box-folder 105/11)
        - Thanks, Piano-conductor score (Box-folder 105/12)
        - That happy ending, Piano-vocal score; No lyric (Box-folder 105/13)
        - That's what I like about you, Short score/full score (Box-folder 105/14)
        - There's a man in my life, Piano-vocal scores(2) (Box-folder 105/15)
        - These foolish things remind me of you, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 105/16)
        - The three b's, Short score (Box-folder 105/17)
        - Ti-pi-tin, Full score, piano-vocal score (Box-folder 129/28)
        - To a wild rose, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 105/18)
        - Modulation, last chorus and coda of To be worthy of you, Full score (Box-folder 105/19)
        - The touch of your hand, Full score (Box-folder 131/4)
        - The touch of your hand, Short score (Box-folder 105/20)
        - Toujours moi? (Are you sure?), Piano score; Music by Don Walker (Box-folder 105/21)
        - Tristan and Isolde, Full score; Incomplete (Box-folder 105/22)
        - The trolley song, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 105/23)
        - 12 days of Christmas, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 105/24)
        - Two of a kind, Published parts; Arranged by Don Walker (Box-folder 105/25)
        - Vive la France, Sketch (Box-folder 105/26)
        - Wait till you see her: waltz ballet, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 105/27)
        - Walsh tune, Piano score (Box-folder 105/28)
        - Waltz material, Sketch (Box-folder 105/29)
        - Water boy, Full score, negative photostat (Box-folder 105/30)
        - The way of dreams, Full score (Box-folder 105/31)
        - The way of dreams, Piano-vocal score, lead sheet; Music by Don Walker (Box-folder 105/32)
        - The way you look tonight, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 105/33)
        - What a way to be!, Piano-vocal scores(3), lyric sheet; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Bix Reichner (Box-folder 105/34)
        - What am I doing here, Lead sheet (Box-folder 105/35)
        - What'll I do, Sketch (Box-folder 106/1)
        - What's real and what's baloney, Lead sheet; Taped photocopy which has been disassembled (Box-folder 106/2)
        - When Stella does the conga at the prom, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 106/3)
        - Who?, Full score; Incomplete (Box-folder 129/29)
        - Who's on thirds?, Full score (Box-folder 129/30)
        - The window cleaners, Piano score/sketch (Box-folder 106/4)
        - Wintergreen for president, Sketch (Box-folder 106/5)
        - With all the love in my heart, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 106/6)
        - Without a song, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 106/7)
        - Wolf step, Piano score/sketch; Unidentified sketch on verso (Box-folder 106/8)
        - A world full of love, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 106/9)
        - Would you be good to baby, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 106/10)
        - You are a welcome love, Piano-vocal score; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Bix Reichner (Box-folder 106/11)
        - You can be kissed, Full score (Box-folder 131/5)
        - Your land and my land, Short score, vocal arrangement (Box-folder 106/12)
        - You're all I need, Parts (Box-folder 106/13)
        - Zing sing-zoom zoom, Vocal arrangement (Box-folder 106/14)
        - Unidentified full scores, Mostly miscellaneous pages (Box-folder 129/31)
        - Miscellaneous and unidentifed music, Sketches, short scores, piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 106/15-16)